http://hamptonct.com/pages/privacy-policy

Simpatico
Smith's Rosebud Perfume Co.
SOAK Bath Co.
Soaps & Soaks From Around the World
Spinster Sisters Co.
The Cottage Greenhouse
The English Soap Co.
Wild Botanicals
Z&Co.
Home
»
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Our Commitment To PrivacyYour privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.We comply with the intent of all the Better Business Bureau OnLine privacy standards.The Information We CollectThis notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Hampton Court website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:NameAddress Email address Phone number The Way We Use InformationWe use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.You can register with our website if you would like to receive updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for any other purpose than that described on the web site.We will never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above.Our Commitment To Data SecurityTo prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Credit Card Information is collected by our partner, Shopify, one of the most trusted names in internet security. They use the latest 128-bit encryption technology to secure personal information. This technology is virtually impossible for anyone to compromise in any way.How To Contact UsShould you have any questions or concerns about these policies, please call send us an email at Contact_Us.
Please visit our other site for Lavender, Eucalyptus and OceanAire scented Heated Spa and Gift ideas!
707-578-9416 or Sales@hamptonct.com. We're here to help!
Smith's Rosebud Perfume Co.
SOAK Bath Co.
Soaps & Soaks From Around the World
Spinster Sisters Co.
The English Soap Co.
Z&Co.
